我还有一年活头了 萨姆
I got a year to live, Sam.
我想好好利用
I'd like to make the most of it.
怎么样 我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
So, what do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
（忆往昔）
我清楚你的感受 迪恩
I know how you feel, Dean.
爸爸死了 他留下了个空洞
Dad's dead, and he left a hole.
你痛苦得难以承受
and it hurts so bad you can't take it.
我没事 好吗
I'm okay. Okay?
我发誓 再有人问我好不好
I swear the next person who asks me if I'm okay,
我就要挥拳头了
I'm gonna start throwing punches.
根本没办法让我不下地狱 是吧
There's no way of saving me from the pit, is there?
对
No.
你死定了
You're gonna die.
这就是你将变成的模样
This is what you're gonna become.
我不想下地狱
I don't wanna go to hell.
我们会想办法救你的
We'll find a way to save you.
你马上解除迪恩的交易
Let Dean out of his deal right now.
我只是推销的
I'm just a saleswoman.
我也像其他人一样有老板
I got a boss like everybody.
合同在谁手里
Who holds the contract?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
来了个新红人
There's a big new up-and-comer.
她叫莉莉丝
Her name is Lilith.
莉莉丝
Lilith?
她真的很想把萨姆的内脏插在棍子上
And she really, really wants Sam's intestines on a stick.
你知道吗
You knew about this?
天啊 萨姆 还有什么我该知道的事吗
Well, jeez, Sam. Is there anything else I should know?
（如今）
- 喂 - 本
- Hello? - Ben.
- 琳达 - 我必须跟你说说话
- Linda. - I had to talk to you.
你不能总往这里打
You can't keep calling here.
我知道
I know, I know.
就…告诉我你考虑过了 求你
Just… Just tell me you thought about it, please.
没什么可考虑的
There's nothing to think about.
别那么说
Don't say that.
我不能
I can't.
你知道我不能 我妻子怎么办
You know I can't. My wife.
我求你 来我这里
I'm begging you. Come to me.
来我这里 本
Come to me, Ben.
不行
No.
琳达 求你
Linda, please.
拜托 放过我吧
Please, just leave me alone.
我不会停下的
I'm not gonna stop.
我想你 本
I miss you, Ben.
我们可以幸福的
We could be happy.
我们可以幸福地在一起
We could be happy together.
这…
This is…
这真是疯了
This is crazy.
我爱你
I love you.
直到永远
Forever.
你不爱我吗
Don't you love me?
你知道我爱你
You know I do.
超过一切
More than anything.
但是…
But…
对不起
I'm sorry.
本 等等
Ben, wait…
好吧 琳达
Okay, Linda.
你赢了
You win.
我来了
I'm coming.
[邪恶力量 第3季第14集]
嗯
Yep.
知道了
I got it.
好 再见
Okay, bye.
怎么样
So?
教授什么都不知道
So the professor doesn't know crap.
震惊啊
Shocking.
- 嗯 - 收拾东西 萨姆
- Yeah. - Pack your panties, Sammy.
我们要上路了
We're hitting the road.
什么 怎么了
What? What's up?
刚刚是鲍比
That was Bobby.
俄亥俄州有个银行家自己爆头了
Some banker guy blew his head off in Ohio,
他觉得可能是鬼魂作祟
and he thinks there's a spirit involved.
你俩在谈案子吗
So you two were talking a case?
不 我们是在谈论我们的情绪
No, we were, uh, we were actually talking about our feelings.
然后又聊了我们最喜欢的男孩乐队
And then our favorite boy bands.
是的 我们在谈案子
Yeah, we were talking a case.
鬼魂吗 怎么回事
So a spirit…? What?
嗯 有个银行家投诉说
Yeah. Well, a banker was complaining.
他家有电力问题 已经一周了
about some electrical problems at his pad for like a week.
电话乱响 电脑闪烁
Phones going haywire. Computers flipping on and off.
你不觉得有问题吗
This is not ringing your bell?
当然有
Well, sure, yeah.
但迪恩 我们在查案呢
But, Dean, we're on a case.
谁的案子
Whose?
你的
Yours.
对哦
Right, yeah.
真能骗过我了
Well, could have fooled me.
那我们最近还在干什么
What the hell else have we been doing lately.
不就是在努力帮你打破交易吗
other than trying to break your deal?
我们就是在白忙活
Chasing our tails, that's what.
萨姆 我们找遍了本土48州所有的教授 女巫
Sam, we've talked to every professor, witch, soothsayer,
算命师 甚至是二流马戏团骗子
and two-bit carny act in the lower 48.
没人知道任何事
Nobody knows squat.
我们也找不到贝拉 或是柯尔特枪
And we can't find Bela. We can't find the Colt.
在我们真找到什么之前
So until we actually find something,
我想好好工作
I'd like to do my job.
- 我们还有个办法没试过 - 不 萨姆
- Look, there's one thing we haven't tried, yet. - No, Sam…
- 不 - 迪恩 我们该召唤露比
- No. - Dean, we should summon Ruby.
我不要再跟你吵这个了
I'm not gonna fight with you.
她说她知道怎么救你
She says she knows how to save you.
她救不了
Well, she can't.
- 是吗 你能确定吗 - 是的
- Really, you know that for sure? - I do.
- 你怎么能确定 - 因为她告诉我了
- How? - Because she told me, okay?
- 什么 - 她告诉我了
- What? - She told me…
直说了
flat out…
她根本救不了我 没人能
that she could not save me. Nobody can.
你就忘记对我说了吗
And you just somehow neglected to mention this to me?
知道吗 我根本不在乎那贱人怎么想
Well, you know, I really don't care what that bitch thinks.
你也不该在乎
and neither should you.
- 所以 - 怎么
- So… - So what?
你现在还对我有隐瞒了 迪恩
Now you're keeping secrets from me, Dean?
你真要谈谁对谁有隐瞒吗
You really wanna talk about who's keeping secrets from who?
你去哪
Now where you going?
看来是要去俄亥俄
Guess I'm going to Ohio.
（俄亥俄州 米兰）
我在那里发现了他
I found him there.
跟我们说说你看到的一切吧 沃特斯太太
Why don't you just tell us everything you saw, Mrs. Waters?
你是说除了我死去的丈夫吗
You mean besides my dead husband?
就说说你看到的其他的一切 拜托
Just everything else you saw, please.
到处是血
There was blood everywhere.
电话被从墙上扯了下来
The phone was ripped from the wall,
桌上摆着他最喜欢的威士忌
his favorite Scotch on the desk.
你们还想知道什么
What else could you possibly wanna know?
电话为什么被从墙上扯了下来
Why was the phone ripped from the wall?
我不知道
I don't know.
我可以看看吗
You mind if I take a look?
我已经跟其他警探都说过了
I already went over all this with the other detectives.
我们很快就离开 女士
We'll be out of your hair in no time, ma'am.
女士 你丈夫什么时候死的
Ma'am, what time did your husband die?
11点之后
Sometime after 11.
有奇怪来电吗
What about strange phone calls?
近来有吗
Receive any of those lately?
奇怪的干扰 静电音 什么的
Weird interference, static, anything like that?
没有
No.
沃特斯太太 对警方隐瞒情况
Mrs. Waters, withholding information from the police.
可是重罪
is a capital offense.
在这世上某些地方肯定是
In some parts of the world, I'm sure.
几周前 有一通…
A couple of weeks ago, uh, there was this…
什么
This what?
我早上醒来
I woke up one morning.
听到本在书房里
I heard Ben in his study.
我以为他在跟个女人通话
I thought he was talking to a woman.
你为什么那么想
What made you think that?
因为他一直喊她琳达
Because he kept calling her Linda.
但是
The thing is…
我拿起了另一部电话
I picked up the other line and.
根本没人打来
nobody was there.
本在对着不存在的人说话
Ben was talking to nobody.
什么都没有吗
There was nothing?
只有静电音
Just static.
你跟本说过这通电话的事吗
Did you ever speak to Ben about this phone call?
没有 我该问的 但没有
No. I should've, but no.
那他说过琳达是谁吗
Did he ever say who Linda was?
这有什么要紧的
What difference does it make?
那边根本没人
There was no one on the other end.
琳达是个美女
Linda's a babe.
生前是
Or was.
- 找到她了 - 嗯 琳达·贝特曼
- Find her? - Yeah, Linda Bateman.
她和本·沃特斯是高中恋人
She and, uh, Ben Waters were high-school sweethearts.
后来呢
So what happened?
被酒驾司机正面撞上
Drunk driver hit them head on.
本活了下来
Ben walked away.
怎么 死去恋人打来聊天吗
So, what then? Dead flame calls to chat?
按说该这么猜
You would think.
但琳达是火化的
But Linda was cremated.
那她的魂怎么还在
So why is she still floating around?
我不知道
You got me.
那个来电显示呢
What about that, uh, caller ID?
原来 那是个电话号码
Turns out it's a phone number.
我可没见过那样的电话号码
It's no phone number I've ever seen.
是啊 因为那是一个世纪前的号码了
Yeah, because it's about a century old,
是电话还有手摇柄时的号码
from back when phones had cranks.
为什么用这个号码来跟人通话
So why use that number to reach out and talk to someone?
这我也不知道
You got me there too,
但不管怎样 我们都该追查一下
but either way, we should run a trace on it.
我们要怎么追查一个
Well, how the hell are we gonna trace a number.
有一百多年历史的号码
that's over 100 years old?
总部一般不会派人过来
We don't get too many folks from HQ down here.
是啊 总部提到这里会安排午餐
Yes, well, the main office mentioned that there would be a lunch.
我们肯定能安排一下
Well, I'm sure we can arrange something.
你们想找的人就在这…
The man you gentlemen wanna be speaking to is right this…
是啊 抱歉
I know. Sorry.
要我说 这下面有点卫生问题
Got something of a hygiene issue down here, if you ask me.
斯杜伊
Stewie?
我不是叫你保持这里干净整洁吗
What did I tell you about keeping this place clean?
垃圾邮件
Spam mail. Spam mail.
斯杜伊·迈耶斯
Stewie Meyers.
这是坎贝尔先生和雷米先生
Mr. Campbell, Mr. Raimi.
我不知道这都怎么来的
I don't know how all this got here.
总部来的
From headquarters.
- 你要满足两位先生的一切需要 - 好
- You give these gentlemen whatever they need. - Yeah.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
有什么能帮你们的
So can I help you?
- 那是丰满亚裔美女网吗 - 不是
- Is that, uh, BustyAsianBeauties.Com? - No.
我好饥渴
Me so horny.
- 可能是吧 - 听我一句
- Maybe. - Word to the wise.
- 白金会员 物有所值 - 嗯 好吧
- Platinum membership. Worth every penny. - Right, anyway.
我们要追踪个号码
We're here to trace a number.
这是哪来的
Where did you get this?
来电显示
Off caller ID.
那不可能
No. That's impossible.
是有些年没用过了 我们知道
Hasn't been used in a few years, we know.
有些年
A few years?
这简直是史前的
It's prehistoric.
- 相信我 现在没人用这个了 - 嗯
- Trust me, nobody's using this number anymore. - Sure.
- 你可以还是查查看吗 - 好
- Could you run it anyway? - Sure.
我先把整个人生都重新安排一下好了
Why don't I just rearrange my whole life first?
听着 斯杜伊
Listen, uh, Stewie.
你这里违反了至少六种员工准则
You got, like, six kinds of employee-code violations down here,
更别提你硬盘上装满了令人作呕的色情片
not to mention the sickening porn clogging up your hard drive.
我搭档叫你查号码
When my partner says run the number,
你最好赶紧查
I suggest you run the number.
好 随便吧 天啊
Okay. Whatever. Jeez.
- 我去 - 怎么了
- Holy crap. - What?
我不知道号码哪来的
I can't tell you where the number comes from.
但我知道它打去了哪
But I can tell you where it's been going.
什么意思
What do you mean?
这两周来有十个住宅
Ten different houses in the past two weeks…
都接到了这个号码的来电
all got calls from the same number.
完事了吗
So are we done here?
因为我还忙着呢
Because I was sort of busy.
懂
Right.
（汽车租赁）
你好
Yeah?
你好 先生 我是电话公司的
Hello, sir. I'm with the phone company.
我们没找电话公司来
We didn't, uh, call the phone company.
是 先生 是我们有事找您
No, sir. No, see, we're calling you.
我们近来接到了这一带的多宗投诉
See, we've had a lot of complaints from the neighborhood, lately.
- 投诉 - 是的 先生
- Complaints? - Yes, sir.
挂断电话 静电音
Dropped calls, static.
甚至是电话那头传来奇怪的声音
Maybe even strange voices on the other end of the line.
不 我们没有这样的情况
No, we haven't had any of that here.
完全没有吗
Nothing?
没有
No.
好 那好 我们就想来问问
Okay, uh, great. Just thought we'd check.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
No problem.
好 走吧
Okay, let's go.
来吧 西蒙
Come on, Simon.
你绝不可能是电话公司的
No way you work for the phone company.
我当然是
Sure I do.
电话公司的人怎么会开租赁汽车
Since when does a phone guy drive a rental or.
穿廉价西装
wear a cheap suit?
是吗
Yeah? Well,
或许我们都有秘密
maybe we're both keeping secrets.
你为什么问我爸是否在电话上听到了什么奇怪声音
Why'd you ask my dad if we heard strange voices on the phone?
- 怎么 你听到什么了吗 - 没有
- Why, did you hear something? - No.
我错了 还以为你听到了什么
My mistake. Thought maybe you did.
我没有 好吗
Well, I didn't, okay?
好 抱歉打扰你了
Okay. Sorry to bother you.
因为
Because, you know…
如果你听到了
if you did,
那我会告诉你
then I would have told you,
我曾经历过你现在经历的事
that I've been right where you're standing right now.
听到声音
Hearing things,
甚至看到无法解释的东西
even seeing things that couldn't be explained.
或许我能帮上忙
Maybe I would have been able to help out a little bit.
好了
Anyways…
等等
Wait.
或许
Maybe…
或许我是跟人通过电话
Maybe I've been talking on the phone,
跟
with…
跟我妈妈
with my mom.
那并不奇怪
Well, that's not so strange.
她死了
She's dead.
死三年了
Like, three years now dead.
她打来的次数多吗
How often does she call you?
有几次吧
A few times.
一周前开始的
It started a week ago.
我还以为我疯了
I thought I was, like, crazy or something.
有件事我可以确定地告诉你
Well, I can tell you one thing for sure.
你得相信我 好吗
And you're gonna have to go with me on this, okay?
你没疯
You're not crazy.
- 嗯 - 哥们
- Yeah. - Dude.
- 这镇上到处有死人给人打电话 - 是啊
- Stiffs are calling people all over town. - Yeah.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
我刚跟个84岁的老奶奶聊过
I just talked to an 84-year-old grandmother,
她近来在跟丈夫电话调情
who's having phone sex with her husband,
死在了朝鲜的丈夫
who died in Korea.
完全改变了我对恋尸癖一词的理解
Completely rocked my understanding of the word necrophilia.
这怎么回事啊 迪恩
So, what the hell's going on here, Dean?
我也不知道 但我们得快点查明
Beats me, but we better find out soon.
这地方要变成鬼魂中枢了
This place is turning into spook central.
是啊
Yeah.
- 好 回头聊 - 嗯
- All right, I'll call you later. - Yeah.
喂 怎么了
Yeah, what?
- 萨姆 - 迪恩
- Sam? - Dean.
迪恩 是你吗
Dean, is that you?
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸吗
I mean, Dad?
你真觉得是爸爸
You really think it was Dad?
我不知道 可能吧
I don't know. Maybe.
他听上去什么样
Well, what did he sound like?
像奥普拉
Like Oprah.
那是爸爸 听上去像爸爸呗 你觉得呢
It was Dad, he sounded like Dad, what do you think?
他说了什么
What did he say?
我的名字
My name.
没别的了吗
That's it?
嗯 通话中断了
Yeah, the call dropped out.
他为什么要来电啊 迪恩
Why would he even call in the first place, Dean?
我不知道 这镇上为什么有鬼给人打电话
I don't know, man. Why are ghosts calling anybody in this town?
但是 有其他人接到亲人的电话
But I mean, other people are hearing from their loved ones.
我们怎么就不能 这至少是个可能性吧
Why can't we? It's at least a possibility, right?
大概吧
Yeah, I guess.
好吧 那或许…
Okay, so what if…?
或许真是爸爸呢
What if it really is Dad?
如果他再打来呢
What happens if he calls back?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我该说什么
What do I say?
你好
Hello.
Hello?
你就想到了这个吗 你好
That's what you come back with? Hello?
你好
Hello?
有发现吗
Find anything?
查了三小时 我没发现任何
After three hours, I have found no reason,
这地方会有超自然现象的理由
why anything supernatural would be going on here.
还以为斯坦福的学历
You know, you'd think a Stanford education,
加上高中完全没泡到过妞
and a high-school hookup rate of 0.0.
会得到更好的结果呢
would produce better results than that.
你真逗
Hilarious.
萨姆 你找错了地方 伙计
Sam, you're just looking in the wrong places, pal.
那该去什么地方找呢 迪恩
And what are the right places, Dean?
旅馆宣传册架
The motel pamphlet rack.
俄亥俄州米兰 托马斯·爱迪生的出生地
Milan, Ohio. Birthplace of Thomas Edison.
嗯 怎么了
Yeah, right. So what?
继续看
Keep reading.
开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
我们继续走
And we're walking.
这是博物馆最独特
And here we have one of the museum's.
最宝贵的珍藏之一
most unique and treasured possessions:
托马斯·爱迪生的「鬼魂电话」
Thomas Edison's "spirit phone."
你们知道吗 爱迪生先生
Did you know that Mr. Edison.
不仅是美国最受喜爱的发明家之一
while being one of America's most beloved inventors.
还醉心于「神秘学」
was also a devout "occultist"?
为什么要打空气引号
What's with the quote-y fingers?
他花了数年研究这件他最后的发明
He spent years working on this, his final invention,
他坚信这台机器可以用来
which he was convinced could be used to.
跟「亡者交流」
"communicate" with the "dead."
很诡异吧
Pretty spooky, huh?
我们继续走 继续走 继续走
And we're walking. We are walking. We're walking.
我们不能碰那个
And we're not touching that.
我们继续走 停下
And we're walking. And stop.
有发现吗
Anything?
没有
Nothing.
你怎么想
What do you think?
老实说
Honestly,
我看就是一堆旧破烂
it kind of looks like an old pile of junk to me.
都没插电
It's not even plugged in.
- 或许不是那么用的 - 好吧
- Maybe it didn't work like that. - Okay.
或许就像个无线电天线塔
Maybe it's like a radio tower, you know?
向全镇广播死人
Broadcasting the dead all over town.
可能吧
Could be.
那个来电号码都有百年历史了 是吧
Well, the you know, the caller ID is 100 years old, right?
正好是这玩意建造出来的时候
Right around the time this thing was built.
是 但它为什么现在突然好用了
Yeah. But why would it all of a sudden start working now?
我不知道
I don't know.
但只要这里还有死人还在给活人打电话
But as long as the moldy are calling the freshes around here,
这就是我们能找到的最好的缘由了
it's the best reason we got.
或许是吧
Yeah, maybe.
所以或许那真是爸爸
So maybe it really is Dad.
爸爸
Dad?
迪恩
Dean.
那真是你吗
Is it really you?
是我
It's me.
- 我怎么能确定 - 你不能
- How can I be sure? - You can't.
迪恩
Dean,
- 你怎么能那么做 - 做什么
- how could you do it? - Do what?
出卖你的灵魂
Sell your soul.
我是在照顾萨姆 像你嘱托的那样
I was looking after Sammy, like you said to.
我可没想要这样
I never wanted this, never.
你是我儿子 我爱你
You're my boy. I love you.
我不能眼看你下地狱 迪恩
I can't watch you go to hell, Dean.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道要怎么阻止
I don't know how to stop it.
因为你破坏交易 萨姆就会死 是吗
Because if you break the deal, Sam dies, right?
- 什么 - 我知道条出路
- What? - Well, I know a way out.
- 你们俩都能解脱 - 怎么做
- For both of you. - How?
那个掌握你合约的恶魔
The demon who holds your contract.
他现在就在这里
He's here. Now.
（好 明天见）
（蕾妮 是你吗）
（妈妈吗）
（我昨晚问了你个问题 你考虑好了吗）
（我不知道你想要什么）
（你当然知道 我想见你）
（我去见你了 去公墓看你了）
（我不是那个意思）
（但我好怕）
（别怕 我就在这里陪你）
（来我这里）
怎么了
What's up?
那姑娘蕾妮
Girl, Lanie,
她妈妈的鬼魂昨晚把她吓得不轻
her mom's ghost spooked her out pretty bad last night.
太可怜了
That sucks.
是啊
Yeah, it does.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我觉得爸爸是对的
I think Dad's right.
我觉得那恶魔是在这里
I think the demon is here.
看看
Check it out.
这是什么 气象报告吗
What is this, weather reports?
是预兆 恶魔预兆
Omens. Demonic omens.
我们这两周来一直被雷暴如影随形
Electrical storms everywhere we've been for the past two weeks.
我不记得看到过雷暴
I don't remember any lightning storms.
我也不记得你小时候研究过气象学呢
I don't remember you studying meteorology as a kid, either.
但相信我 那混蛋一直在跟着我
But I'm telling you, that bastard's been tailing me,
用了不知哪个可怜人的肉身
wearing some poor dude's meat.
它跟踪你是因为
And it's following you because…?
因为我是个大猎物
I guess I'm big game, you know?
太宝贝了 不想让我脱离视线
My ass is too sweet to let out of sight.
好吧
Okay, sure.
别太激动啊 萨姆
Don't get too excited, Sammy.
别拉伤了哪里
Might pull something.
迪恩 听着 我也想相信
Dean, look, I wanna believe this, man.
- 真的 - 那就相信吧
- I really do… - Then believe it.
如果我们抓到这混蛋
I mean, if we get this sucker,
那就大功告成了
it's Miller Time.
是啊 这是另一个问题
Yeah, that's another thing.
爸爸说出了一个能杀死恶魔的驱魔仪式
Dad rattles off an exorcism that can kill a demon.
不仅仅是把它送回地狱 还能杀了它
Not just send it back to hell, but kill it?
我查过了
I've checked it out.
这是黑暗时代的厉害玩意
This is heavy-duty Dark Ages.
15世纪的
Fifteenth century.
嗯 我也查过了 迪恩
Yeah, I checked on it too, Dean.
鲍比也查了
And so did Bobby.
好 那怎么样
Okay. And?
听着
Look,
这绝对是个驱魔仪式
it definitely is an exorcism, okay?
但并无证据表明它能杀死恶魔
There's just no evidence that it can kill a demon.
也没证据表明它不能
No evidence it can't.
迪恩 拜托
Dean, come on…
据我所知
As far as I know,
我们之中只有爸爸真去过地狱
the only one of us that's actually been to hell is Dad. Okay?
或许他在下面学会了点招数
Maybe he picked up a couple of tricks down there,
比如哪种驱魔仪式好用
like which exorcisms work.
或许是吧
Maybe it does, okay?
我也希望好用 但我们得确定一下
Look, I hope it does too, but we just gotta be sure.
我们怎么不确定了
Why aren't we sure?
因为我不知道这里究竟是什么情况 迪恩
Because I don't know what's going on around here, Dean.
有个人吞枪自尽了
I mean, some guy blows his brains out,
一个小女孩吓坏了
a little girl is scared out of her wits.
天啊 几个平民被鬼吓坏了
Man, a couple of civvies are freaked out by some ghosts.
告诉你 萨姆 人们就是会被鬼吓坏
News flash, Sam, people are supposed to be freaked out by ghosts.
爸爸告诉你去哪找那个恶魔了吗
Dad tell you where to find the demon?
我还在等电话
I'm waiting on the call.
我告诉蕾妮我会去看她了
I told Lanie I'd stop by.
好啊 不 你去找幼女吧
Good, yeah. No, you go hang out with jailbait.
小心着点克里斯·汉森（钓鱼执法的电视记者）
Just, uh, watch out for Chris Hansen.
而我会在这里 等着救我自己的命
Meanwhile, I'll be here, you know, getting ready to save my life.
你真是难以置信
You are unbelievable, you know that?
几个月来 我们一直在努力打破这个恶魔交易
I mean, for months we've been trying to break this demon deal.
爸爸马上要告诉我们地址了
Now, Dad's about to give us the frigging address,
你却不肯接受
and you can't accept it?
他都死了 你还跟他对着干
The man's dead and you're still butting heads with the guy.
- 才不是为了这个 - 那是为了什么
- That's not what this is about. - Then what is?
事实就是 我们没有切实证据 迪恩
The fact is, we got no hard proof here, Dean.
经历了这么多 你还是盲目相信
After everything, you're still just going on blind faith.
是啊 或许吧 或许我只有这个
Yeah, well, maybe. You know, maybe that's all I got, okay?
求你
Please.
我回来之前哪都别去 好吗 迪恩
Just please don't go anywhere until I get back, okay, Dean?
求你
Please.
你跟你父亲说过这些吗
Have you told your father about any of this?
打扰他工作吗
And bother him at work?
没有
No.
他反正也不会相信我
He wouldn't believe me, anyway.
他只会让我去接受治疗
He'd just chuck me into therapy.
你妈妈怎么说的
So, what did your mother say?
她说想见我
That she wanted to see me.
起初 我以为是要我去公墓
So at first I thought I was supposed to go to the cemetery.
- 你去了吗 - 没发生什么
- Did you? - Nothing happened.
但之后 她又要我做别的事
But then she started asking me to do other things.
什么别的事
What sort of things?
坏事
Bad things.
喂 我是西蒙·格林菲尔德
Hello? Simon Greenfield speaking.
妈妈
Mommy.
嗯 我想见你 你在哪
Yeah, I wanna see you. Where are you?
- 爸爸 - 迪恩
- Dad? - Dean.
那恶魔在哪
Where's the demon?
蕾妮 拜托
Lanie, please.
告诉我发生了什么 这很重要
Tell me what happened. It's very important.
妈妈叫我去翻爸爸的药柜
Mom told me to go to Dad's medicine cabinet.
然后呢
And?
服他的安眠药 他所有的安眠药
Take his sleeping pills. Take all his sleeping pills.
她要你自杀吗
She wanted you to kill yourself?
我妈妈为什么会要我那么做
Why would my mom want me to do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
就为了让我去她那里吗
I mean, just so I could come to her?
你说什么
What'd you say?
- 她要我去她那里 - 不不
- She wanted me to come to her. - No, no, no.
她具体怎么说的
How did she say it exactly?
「来我这里」说了好多次
"Come to me." like, a million times.
蕾妮
Lanie.
那不是你妈妈
That's not your mother.
听我说 别接电话 别用电脑
Listen to me. Don't answer the phone. Don't use the computer.
别做任何我没叫你做的事 好吗
Don't do anything unless I say to, all right?
蕾妮
Lanie.
西蒙呢
Where's Simon?
有人吗
Hello?
迪恩 不是爸爸
Dean, it's not Dad.
- 那是什么 - 是克洛卡塔
- Then what is it? - A crocotta.
- 那是种三明治吗 - 是种食腐动物
- That a sandwich? - Some kind of scavenger.
能模仿亲人声音
Mimics loved ones.
低语「来我这里」
Whispers, "come to me."
把你引入黑暗中 然后吞食你的灵魂
Then lures you into the dark and swallows your soul.
克洛卡塔 好 这就说得通了
Crocotta, right. Damn, that makes sense.
迪恩 听着 抱歉
Dean, look, I'm sorry, man.
- 我知道… - 这玩意生活在脏的地方吧
- I know… - Don't these things live in filth?
- 对 - 萨姆 电话公司的苍蝇
- Yeah. - Sam, the flies at the phone company.
我是赫曼·蒙斯特 请留言
It's Herman Munster. Leave a message.
迪恩 我在停车场 他在这里
Dean, I'm in the parking lot. He's here.
快点来
Hurry.
搞什么
What the hell?
- 我知道你是什么 - 等等 先生
- I know what you are. - Wait, mister.
- 我也知道怎么杀了你 - 拜托
- And I know how to kill you. - Please.
好吧 等等
Okay, wait, wait.
如果我们多收了你的呼叫等待费用什么的
If we're overcharging you for the call waiting or something, I…
这我可以解决 我是你的朋友
I can fix that, I'm your friend.
拜托 别杀我
Please. Just… Just don't kill me.
别杀我 求你
Don't kill me, please.
好样的
Yeah.
谁叫你敢惹电话公司 蠢蛋
That's what happens when you mess with the phone company, dillweed.
谢谢 克拉克
Thank you, Clark.
别客气
Forget about it.
克拉克
Clark?
对不起 克拉克
I… I'm sorry, Clark.
不管我对你做了什么 对不起
I'm sorry for whatever I did to you.
- 对不起 求你 - 等等
- I'm sorry. Please… - Wait.
等等 别
Wait. Don't do it.
你醒了
You're awake.
你不是个杀手 克拉克 不是
You're not a killer, Clark. No.
你心里有个好人的 我知道
There's a good man inside of you. I know it.
你觉得呢 萨姆
What do you think, Sammy?
我是个好人吗
Am I a good man?
放了他吧
Just let him go.
我想的
I would.
我真挺想的
I really would.
可惜我中午只吃了份沙拉
If only I'd had more than a salad for lunch.
你瞧
You see?
我饿死了
I'm starving.
不
No!
我最后跟道恩的那通电话
My last call with Dean…
那是你
That was you.
你把我引来了这里
You led me here.
我会打电话 也会接电话
Some calls I make, some calls I take.
但你得承认
But you have to admit,
我骗过了你一阵
I had you fooled for a while.
爱迪生那台电话的鬼扯
All that Edison phone crap.
好吧
Well.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在杀你哥哥
I'm killing your brother.
也或者我是在杀另一个人
Or maybe I'm killing another guy.
我们得等着瞧了
We'll just have to see how it goes.
喂
Hello?
爸爸
Daddy.
宝贝
Baby.
你不是说你不会再打来了吗
I thought you said you weren't gonna call anymore.
我知道 爸爸
I know, Daddy.
你知道这让老爸多难过
You know how sad this makes your old man.
我在你葬礼上多难过
How upset I was at your funeral.
我必须打来 我知道是谁杀了我 爸爸
I had to call. I know who killed me, Daddy.
什么
What?
杀我的男人 他现在就在家里
The man who killed me. He's at the house right now.
什么 你在说什么
What? What are you saying to me?
他在家里呢 爸爸 他还想杀你
He's at the house, Daddy. He wants to kill you too.
模仿迪恩是一回事
You know, mimicking Dean's one thing.
但我爸
But my dad,
那真是厉害了
that's a hell of a trick.
我一发现你俩是猎人 就很简单了
Well, once I made you two as hunters, it was easy.
查到了迪恩的号码
Found Dean's number…
然后是你的号码
then your number,
然后是你爸爸的几个号码
then your father's numbers.
还有电邮
Then to e-mails,
语音信箱
voice mails.
一切
Everything.
人们以为那些东西会被抹去
You see, people think that that stuff just gets erased.
但它不会
But it doesn't.
你想不到
You'd be surprised at.
你有多少信息散落在外面
how much of yourself is just floating out there…
等着被提取出来
waiting to be plucked.
迪恩不会上当的
Dean's not gonna fall for this.
他不会杀了那人的
He's not gonna kill that guy.
那么那人便会杀了他
Then the guy kills him.
科技
Technology.
让生活简便多了
Makes life so much easier.
以前 我要在林子里藏几天 几周
Used to be I'd hide in the woods for days, weeks…
对人低语
whispering to people.
想把他们从黑夜里引出来
Trying to draw them out into the night.
但他们有社区
But they had community.
他们彼此照顾
They all looked out after each other.
我一年能吃一两个灵魂就算走运了
I'd be lucky to eat maybe one, two souls a year.
但现在我饿了时 我只需要打个电话
But now when I'm hungry, I simply make a phone call.
你们都连接在一起
You're all so connected.
但却前所未有的孤独
But you've never been so alone.
这是什么
What is this?
你的葬礼
Your funeral.
你对我女儿也这么做了吗
You did this to my daughter too?
你怎么走出来的
How the hell did you get out?
你对我女儿也这么做了吗
You do this to my daughter too?
等等 这是搞错了
Wait. This is a mistake.
你杀了她
You killed her.
- 不 等等 - 你杀了她 你个混蛋
- No. Wait. - You killed her, you son of a bitch.
- 她才九岁 - 住手
- She was 9 years old! - Stop.
我没
I didn't.
你得相信我
You gotta believe me.
你为什么杀她
Why did you kill her?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没杀你女儿
I didn't kill your daughter.
那你在这里干什么
Then what are you doing here?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们改善了你的脸呢
I see they improved your face.
嗯 你也是
Yeah, right back at you.
克洛卡塔啊
So crocotta, huh?
是啊
Yep.
怪不得有苍蝇呢
That would explain the flies.
是啊
Yeah, it would.
很遗憾不是爸爸
Look, I'm sorry it wasn't Dad.
不 我这次对你态度好差
No, I gave you a hell of a time on this one.
不 你是对的
No, you were right.
别去想了
Forget about it.
我做不到
I can't.
我太想相信这事还有出路了
I wanted to believe so badly that there was a way out of this.
我真是穷途末路了
I mean, I'm staring down the barrel at this thing.
地狱啊
You know, hell.
真格的 永不得翻身 我…
For real, forever. And I'm just…
嗯
Yeah.
我好怕 萨姆
I'm scared, Sam.
我真的好怕
I'm really scared.
我知道
I know.
我大概是愿意相信一切了
I guess I was willing to believe anything.
绝望之人的最后一搏
You know, last act of a desperate man.
- 有希望没什么不对 迪恩 - 不
- There's nothing wrong with having hope, Dean. - No.
希望不能让你得到什么
Hope doesn't get you jack squat.
我不能指望
I can't expect.
爸爸会在最后时刻带着奇迹出现
Dad to show up with some miracle at the last minute.
我不能指望任何人
I can't expect anybody to, you know?
唯一能帮我脱身的就是我自己
And the only person that can get me out of this thing is me.
还有我
And me.
「还有我」
"And me"?
怎么了
What?
倾吐内心 气氛刚刚好
Deep revelation, having a real moment here,
你就想到了这个吗
that's what you come back with?
「还有我」
"And me"?
- 你要我写诗吗 - 那气氛过去了
- Do you want a poem? - Moment's gone.
难以置信
Unbelievable.